<Document>
  # Head of Personnel
  Well, well, well. If it isn't the one, the only, Head of Paperwork. Get your gloves on, it's time to get cracking.

  The Head of Personnel is the head of the Service department as well as the manager of all the IDs on the station.
  Your duties include overseeing your chefs, bartenders and botanists as well as coordinating between the other departments and having them get along.

  But most importantly-- you change IDs.

  ## Changing IDs
  To get started, you need your own ID, someone else's ID and an ID card computer.
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HoPIDCard" Caption="your ID card"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PassengerIDCard" Caption="someone else's ID card"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerId"/>
  </Box>

  Now, follow these steps.
  - First, put your ID into the computer. This is the Privileged ID, the one that has the ability to modify other cards.
  - Now, put in the ID you want to change. This is the target ID. You're modifying the access of this one.
  - Choose a preset. This will change the person's job icon that will show up on secHUDs and the crew manifest.
  - If necessary, add or take away additional accesses.
  - Take out the IDs and make sure you don't accidentally hand someone else your own ID!

  ## Access Types
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirlockCommand" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HighSecDoor" Caption=""/>
    Command gives access to the bridge and the vault, but not department head rooms.
  </Box>
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirlockSecurity" Caption=""/>
    Brig gives access to security's lobby. Security gives access to Security equipment, excluding the Armory.
  </Box>
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirlockServiceLocked" Caption=""/>
    Service allows access into general service areas, but not specific service rooms as they have their own accesses, like the Bar.
  </Box>
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirlockCargo" Caption=""/>
    Research allows into Science and Robotics. The R&D server is usually locked behind a Research Director airlock.
  </Box>
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirlockMedical" Caption=""/>
    Medical does not allow access into Cryogenics or Chemistry, as they have their own accesses.
  </Box>
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirlockEngineering" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirlockAtmospherics" Caption=""/>
    Engineering does not allow access into Atmospherics or outside the station, as they have their own accesses.
  </Box>
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirlockCargo" Caption=""/>
   Cargo does not allow access into Salvage, as it has its own access.
  </Box>
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirlockMaint" Caption=""/>
    Maintenance allows access into the maintenance shafts but not the substation rooms.
  </Box>
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirlockExternal" Caption=""/>
    External access allows people to leave the station, either for a spacewalk or a one-way trip.
  </Box>
</Document>
